

Abdessalem Letaief

Computer science engineering student

Arriving at the end of my studies as a computer science engineer which concludes three years of polyvalent training, I am now ready to start a new experience during which I aspire to put my skills in service of an innovative project in WEB development.

Work experience

Part time web developer / Fitness French federation Tunisia

From July 2019 to December 2019

- -Development of a membership management platform for the Fitness French Federation
- -Design and development of the UI by creating responsive pages using Bootstrap and Angular Material.
- -Design, creation of the data base Structure and models.
- -Development of the REST API, HTTP requests at the backend using ExpressJs library, and the Angular services to receive data From these requests.

Angular 8, NodeJs, Express, MongoDB, JWT, JavaScript, GIT, Angular material

Internship / Factoorya Sousse

From July 2019 to September 2019

Creation of an energy consumption monitoring platform that communicates with IOT cards via REST API.

- -Creation and design of the REST API database and communication service models with access restriction.
- -Development of the Front-End part and web pages dynamic and reactive with the restriction to roads.

Django, Angular 8, MySQL, Angular Material, GIT

Internship / Mobelite Monastir

From July 2018 to September 2018

Development of an HR management platform for the hosting company.

- -Conception of the UI using HTML and Bootstrap as CSS library.
- -Development of the Backend using Symphony 4 and MySQL as a database .

Symfony4,HTML,CSS,JS, MySQL

Education

Computer science engineer / National school of engineering of Sousse Sousse Tunisia

From September 2017 to January 2020

Pre-Engineering study / Preparatory Institute for Engineering Studies of Monastir Monastir

From September 2015 to June 2017

Baccalaureate / Bourguiba high school Monastir

From September 2014 to June 2015

▼ Abdesalemletaief@gmail.com

m Date of birth 03/28/1996

+216 28 350 231

Projects

Social Media (on going) Development of a social network dedicated to athletes

Spring Boot, JEE, ReactJS, MongoDB

CV creation plateforme Realization of a CV creation plateforme.

Angular 7, ExpressJS, MongoDB, NodeJS

Risk prediction plateforme for the Tunisian court of audit Risk prediction plateforme for the Tunisian court of audit

Angular, Flask, Python

Web site Development of a web site for an event HTML, CSS, JS

Skills

Front-End

Angular8/React/TypeScript/HTML/CSS/Js Bootstrap

Back-End

Django/NodeJS/Express/ASP.net/JEE

Others

Python/Java/C, C++, C#/PHP/Git/Docker/IBM Cloud

Soft Skills

Leadership / Public Speaking / Communication / Stress Management

Voluntary experience

Treasurer (2018-2019) JEENISo Treasury Process Pilot (ISO 9001 V Certified 2015)

Chief Of design and web development at FCEE'8 Leader of the design and development team at FCEE'8

Hult Prise Organizer 2018

Languages

Arabic Mother Tongue

English Toiec B2 score (935)

French Professional